She’s watching. She’s waiting. She wants your life.
Another Me is a thriller, mystery, horror film directed by Isabel Coixet.
A teenager finds her perfect life upended when she's stalked by a mysterious
doppelganger who has her eyes set on assuming her identity.
Fay Delussey / Lila Delussey, played by Sophie Turner.
Ann Delussey, played by Claire Forlani.
Don Delussey, played by Rhys Ifans.
Doctor Carbantes, played by Eugenio Pérez.
Drew Fraser, played by Gregg Sulkin.
Dawn, played by Priyanka Patel.
Another Me (Spanish: Mi otro yo) is a 2013 psychological thriller drama film directed by Isabel Coixet and starring
Sophie Turner (in her film debut), Jonathan Rhys Meyers, Claire Forlani, Rhys Ifans, and Gregg Sulkin.
It is based on the 2003 novel of the same name by Catherine MacPhail.
The film had its world premiere at the Rome Film Festival on 15 November 2013.
The film was released in Spain on 27 June 2014 and in
the United States on 22 August 2014.
The tone is dark and mind_bending and emotional.